Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Grand Register (Box 89)
  - Grand Register (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Oversize.
- Financial Records - Cash Ledger 1 (Box 90)
  - Financial Records - Cash Ledger of Switchmen's Union of North America, 1901-1906 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    Oversized Bound Volume. Manuscript. 1901-1906 Number 1.
- Financial Records - Cash Ledger 1 (Box 90)
- Financial Records - Cash Ledger 2 (Box 91)
  - Financial Records - Cash Ledger, 1906-1911 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    Oversized Bound Volume. Manuscript. 1906-1911 Number 2.
- Financial Records - Cash Ledger 2 (Box 91)
- Financial Records - Cash Ledger 3 (Box 92)
- Financial Records - Cash Ledger 3 (Box 92)
  - Financial Records - Cash Ledger, 1911-1917 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    Oversized Bound Volume. Manuscript. 1911-1917 Number 3.
- Switchmen's Arbitration (Box 93)
  - Switchmen's Arbitration Volume 1, 1910 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    March 4-22, 1910
  - Switchmen's Arbitration Volume 2, 1910 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1916-1919 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1920-1929 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1949 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements - Circulars, 1922-1925 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Your New Railroad Retirement Act, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Secret Work, 1921-1922 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Blank Forms (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Claims Department Ledger Volumes 1-6 (Box 94)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 1, 1901-1908 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 2, 1908-1914 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 3, 1914-1922 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 4, 1922-1930 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 5, 1930-1942 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    Bound Volume. Manuscript
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 6, 1942-1946 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Claims Department Ledger Volumes 7-9; Miscellaneous Reports; Exhibits (Box 95)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 7, 1946-1954 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 8, 1954-1959 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Claims Department Ledger Volume 9, 1959-1964 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Reports (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Exhibits Submitted by the Special Conference Committee of the Railways in the Switchmen's Union Arbitration, 1916 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    New York, 1916. S.E. Heberling.
- SUNA Charters, Railroad Charters, etc. for SUNA Lodge 298, Jersey City (Box 96)
- SUNA Cartoons -- but one removed and placed in box 273 (Box 97)
- SUNA Cartoons (Box 98)
- SUNA Cartoons (Box 98)